=The Little Red Matchmaker= =Episode 9=
=صانع الثقاب الأحمر الصغير= =الحلقة 9=
Ahh.
اه.
Hey.
يا.
I've known little.
لقد عرفت القليل.
Only now do I understand
الآن فقط أفهم
that meeting Lone Wolf would make you
أن لقاء لون وولف من شأنه أن يجعلك
regret for your whole life.
الندم على حياتك كلها.
Hmph.
همف.
Ahh...
اه...
He is so handsome.
انه وسيم جدا.
Do you know
هل تعرف
at that time
فى ذلك التوقيت
my horse got frightened,
حصاني أصبح خائفا
and there were cliffs ahead?
وكانت هناك المنحدرات المقبلة؟
I was extremely scared.
كنت خائفة للغاية.
Suddenly,
فجأة،
Lone Wolf came down from the sky
نزل لون وولف من السماء
and saved me.
وأنقذني.
Miss,
يفتقد،
are you okay?
هل أنت بخير؟
Lone Wolf is the most handsome man
لون وولف هو الرجل الأكثر وسامة
in the world.
فى العالم.
What about Master?
ماذا عن المعلم؟
Don't mention him.
لا تذكره.
He is just a blockhead,
فهو مجرد أحمق،
and not handsome at all.
وليس وسيمًا على الإطلاق.
Come on, and don't just look at it.
هيا، ولا تنظر إليها فقط.
Pork head is delicious.
رأس لحم الخنزير لذيذ.
Changqing,
تشانغتشينغ،
it's not that I want to keep Miss Mei.
ليس الأمر أنني أريد الاحتفاظ بالآنسة مي.
I really can't send her away.
أنا حقا لا أستطيع أن أرسلها بعيدا.
Miss Mei, here are some food and water.
آنسة مي، إليك بعض الطعام والماء.
Before the sun goes down,
قبل أن تغرب الشمس،
hurry on your way.
اسرع في طريقك.
Master,
يتقن،
I'm lost.
أنا تائه.
Hmmm.
أمم.
If you don't have basic skills,
إذا لم تكن لديك المهارات الأساسية،
how can you join me in robbing the rich to aid the poor?
كيف يمكنك الانضمام إلي في سرقة الأغنياء لمساعدة الفقراء؟
Stay focused!
حافظ على تركيزك!
Okay.
تمام.
Master, I'm lost again.
سيدي، لقد فقدت مرة أخرى.
Come on.
تعال.
Thank you, Lone Wolf.
شكرا لك، لون وولف.
It will trouble you
سوف يزعجك
to take care of Siyue.
لرعاية Siyue.
OK.
نعم.
Ahh?
اه؟
Well, I still think Master is more handsome.
حسنًا، ما زلت أعتقد أن السيد أكثر وسامة.
Hmmm?
أمم؟
Lone Wolf is handsome.
لون وولف وسيم.
All right, Miss Mei, I get it.
حسنًا يا آنسة مي، فهمت الأمر.
You like Lone Wolf now.
أنت تحب لون وولف الآن.
I'm not.
أنالست.
I don't want any more men.
لا أريد المزيد من الرجال.
I don't believe that.
لا أعتقد ذلك.
It's true.
انها حقيقة.
I'll no longer fall for any man.
لن أقع في حب أي رجل بعد الآن.
We
نحن
must be strong and independent.
يجب أن تكون قوية ومستقلة.
After falling for a man,
بعد الوقوع في حب رجل
we find it hard
نجد ذلك صعبا
to wander through the world.
للتجول في العالم.
Hmmm.
أمم.
Let me tell you.
دعني أخبرك.
No man
لا يوجد انسان
is good.
جيد.
Therefore,
لذلك،
I swear now
أقسم الآن
to stay away from men.
للابتعاد عن الرجال.
I,
أنا،
Mei Siyue.
مي سيوي.
I, Liu Yingying.
أنا، ليو ينغ يينغ.
Swear to Yue Lao
أقسم ليوي لاو
that we will ignore bad men from now on,
أننا سوف نتجاهل الرجال السيئين من الآن فصاعدا،
and not fall into the love trap.
وعدم الوقوع في فخ الحب.
I don't think we just deny everything
لا أعتقد أننا ننكر كل شيء
due to transient displeasure.
بسبب استياء عابر.
For Lone Wolf,
للذئب الوحيد،
we can give him another chance.
يمكننا أن نعطيه فرصة أخرى.
If once is not okay,
إذا لم تكن مرة واحدة على ما يرام،
then just twice.
ثم مرتين فقط.
Yue Lao, what I just said is wrong.
يو لاو، ما قلته للتو خطأ.
Don't listen to me.
لا تستمع لي.
Improper friends ruin one's whole life.
الأصدقاء غير المناسبين يدمرون حياة المرء بأكملها.
Woops!
عفوًا!
Oh,
أوه،
Changqing,
تشانغتشينغ،
you should rest early.
يجب أن ترتاح مبكراً.
I'll go back.
سأعود.
You...
أنت...
Why did you apply such ugly makeup on me?
لماذا وضعت مثل هذا المكياج القبيح علي؟
I'm afraid those bandits
أخشى أن هؤلاء قطاع الطرق
would fancy you.
سوف يتوهم لك.
Am I so good-looking?
هل أنا حسن المظهر إلى هذا الحد؟
As I drank too much,
كما شربت كثيرا،
I eat something
أنا آكل شيئا
to warm up.
القيام بالتسخين.
Hey.
يا.
Don't you know
لا تعلم
that you should respect the master?
أنه يجب عليك احترام السيد؟
I shall eat first.
سأأكل أولا.
Wait.
انتظر.
Respect the old and love the meat.
احترم القديم وأحب اللحوم.
Master, don't you like meat?
سيدي، ألا تحب اللحوم؟
It's respecting the old and loving the young.
إنه احترام الكبار وحب الصغار.
OK.
نعم.
(To be continued) It's said that those who catch fireflies
(يتبع) ويقال أن الذين يصطادون اليراعات
are meant to be together.
من المفترض أن نكون معًا.
♪When the wind ceases♪
♪ عندما تتوقف الريح ♪
♪It's the fisherman's song♪
♪إنها أغنية الصياد♪
♪As the moonlit night is drawing on♪
♪ مع اقتراب الليل المقمر ♪
♪A solitary wild goose is flying in the fog♪
♪ أوزة برية منفردة تطير في الضباب ♪
♪The waning moon is deep in thought♪
♪ القمر المتضائل غارق في التفكير ♪
♪Shedding a golden light over the road♪
♪ إلقاء ضوء ذهبي على الطريق ♪
♪I'm longing for returning home♪
♪ أنا مشتاق للعودة إلى المنزل ♪
♪I abandoned cultivation for a new life♪
♪ لقد تخليت عن الزراعة من أجل حياة جديدة ♪
♪And for the beauty in my heart♪
♪ وللجمال الذي في قلبي ♪
♪We meet only in dreams♪
♪نلتقي فقط في الأحلام♪
♪Souls entwine over the time♪
♪تتشابك الأرواح مع مرور الوقت♪
♪The shattered fate breaks the bond♪
♪ المصير المحطم يكسر الرابطة ♪
♪Years pass by like a dream♪
♪السنوات تمر كالحلم ♪
♪My yearning turns into a melody♪
♪يتحول شوقي إلى لحن♪
♪You are my eternal love in heart♪
♪أنت حبي الأبدي في القلب♪
♪My past life fades like clouds dispersing♪
♪ حياتي الماضية تتلاشى مثل تفرق السحب ♪
♪As I meet you in this life♪
♪ كما التقيت بك في هذه الحياة ♪
♪A thousand years of waiting is not in vain♪
♪ ألف سنة من الانتظار لم تذهب سدى ♪
♪Dreaming in a cool, long night♪
♪ أحلم في ليلة باردة طويلة ♪
♪Who is waiting alone♪
♪ من ينتظر وحده ♪
♪My endless yearning stretches on♪
♪ يمتد شوقي الذي لا نهاية له ♪
♪Despite the hard fate♪
♪ رغم المصير الصعب ♪
♪I hope to reconnect with you♪
♪أتمنى إعادة التواصل معك♪
♪And spend the rest of my life with you♪
♪ وأقضي بقية حياتي معك ♪